I have to admit that I have a little
tengo que reconocer que tengo ahí una
doubt about whether García Montes could
dudilla de si García Montes se puede
get away with it and get
llegar a salir con la suya y conseguir
Daniel Sancho to be
que Daniel Sancho dentro de 4 años esté
in Spain, Finland, in 4 years' time. At the moment, because the
en España Finlandia de momento porque la
Samui prosecutor's office already has
fiscalía de samui ya tiene en su poder
the first major police report on the
el primer gran informe policial del caso
Sancho case, the officers already recognize that there was
Sancho los agentes ya reconocen que
a previous fight between
existió una pelea previa entre la
Daniel Sancho's victim, they could
víctima de Daniel Sancho podría
rule out the aggravating circumstance of treachery and
descartar el agravante de alevosía y por
therefore they could, I don't know if they could turn the
tanto podría no sé si dar la vuelta al
case around. No, man, the turn around, the turn around the
caso No hombre la vuelta la vuelta al
case, not lower
caso no bajar en bastantes grados la
Daniel Sancho's sentence by enough degrees and certainly
pena de Daniel Sancho y desde luego
save him from the death penalty. Yes, save him from the
librarle de la pena de muerte sí
death penalty. Yes, yes, they
librarle de la pena de muerte Sí sí
could,
podría sale de la cárcel por primera vez
Daniel Sancho has seen the light of day because he has
Daniel Sancho ha visto la luz Porque ha
left prison to receive
salido de la prisión para recibir una
important news.
importante noticia